<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Module 6_2 page 1 -->
    <!-- int[] module6_2_1 = {0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0}; -->
    <string name="module6_2_1_title">UNAMBIGUOUS GRAMMAR</string>
    <string name="module6_2_1_content_1">In this lesson, we will dive into the critical role that
grammar plays in crafting clear and precise sentences. Unambiguous grammar can lead to
misunderstandings, misinterpretations, and confusion. To communicate effectively, it's essential to
structure sentences in a way that leaves no room for uncertainty. This module will equip you with the
tools to recognize and correct ambiguous grammatical constructs, ensuring that your communication
remains concise, accurate, and unambiguous.</string>
    <string name="module6_2_1_content_2"></string>

    <!-- Module 6_2 page 2 -->
    <!-- int[] module6_2_2 = {0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0}; -->
    <string name="module6_2_2_title"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_2_content_1">This module is likely focused on teaching unambiguous
grammar—grammatical structures that ensure clarity and precision in communication. The lessons may
include identifying common grammatical ambiguities, exercises to practice rewriting ambiguous
sentences, and examples of how small changes in sentence structure can dramatically improve clarity.
The emphasis is on effective, error-free communication that leaves no room for confusion.</string>
    <string name="module6_2_2_content_2"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_2_content_3"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_2_content_4"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_2_content_5"></string>

    <string name="module6_2_2_content_6"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_2_content_7"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_2_content_8"></string>

    <!-- Module 6_2 page 3 -->
    <!-- int[] module6_2_3 = {0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 2, 0, 0}; -->
    <string name="module6_2_3_title"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_3_content_1">Basic Examples of Unambiguous Grammar:</string>
    <string name="module6_2_3_content_2">Ambiguous Sentence: The professor discussed the project
with the student in the office.</string>
    <string name="module6_2_3_content_3">Unambiguous Version: In the office, the professor discussed
the project with the student.</string>
    <string name="module6_2_3_content_4">Ambiguous Sentence: The man saw the woman with a
telescope.</string>
    <string name="module6_2_3_content_5">Unambiguous Version: Using a telescope, the man saw the
woman.</string>
    <string name="module6_2_3_content_6"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_3_content_7"></string>
    <string name="module6_2_3_content_8"></string>

</resources>