<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Module 5_1 page 1 -->
    <!-- int[] module5_1_1 = {0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0}; -->
    <string name="module5_1_1_title">PARSE TREES AND IT’S CONSTRUCTION</string>
    <string name="module5_1_1_content_1">In this module, we will dive into one of the core concepts in
computational linguistics and formal grammar. Parse trees play a crucial role in the world of syntax,
allowing us to break down and understand the structure of sentences and expressions. Whether you\'re
new to parsing or have some experience, this lesson will help you build a solid foundation in constructing
and interpreting parse trees.</string>
    <string name="module5_1_1_content_2"></string>

    <!-- Module 5_1 page 2 -->
    <!-- int[] module5_1_2 = {0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0}; -->
    <string name="module5_1_2_title"></string>
    <string name="module5_1_2_content_1">Parse trees, also known as syntax trees, represent the
syntactic structure of a string according to a given grammar. Each node in the tree represents a grammar
rule, and the leaves of the tree represent the terminal symbols (the actual elements of the input). Parse
trees are essential in compilers and natural language processing as they enable us to check the correct
structure of input data based on a set of grammatical rules. The construction of a parse tree involves
starting from the root (the start symbol of the grammar) and working through the production rules until
the input is fully parsed.</string>
    <string name="module5_1_2_content_2">Basic Examples:</string>
    <string name="module5_1_2_content_3">Mathematical Expression Parsing: For the expression 3 + (4
* 5), the parse tree would break it down into:</string>
    <string name="module5_1_2_content_4">The root representing the + operation</string>

    <string name="module5_1_2_content_5">Two branches: one for the number 3 and another for the
multiplication 4 * 5</string>

    <!-- Module 5_1 page 3 -->
    <!-- int[] module5_1_3 = {0, 1, 2, 2, 2, 0}; -->
    <string name="module5_1_3_title"></string>
    <string name="module5_1_3_content_1">Sentence Parsing in English: For the sentence "The cat
sleeps," a simple parse tree would look like:</string>
    <string name="module5_1_3_content_2">The root node represents a sentence (S).</string>
    <string name="module5_1_3_content_3">Branches for noun phrase (NP: "The cat") and verb phrase
(VP: "sleeps").</string>
    <string name="module5_1_3_content_4">The noun phrase further breaks down into a determiner
(Det: "The") and a noun (N: "cat").</string>
    <string name="module5_1_3_content_5"></string>
    <string name="module5_1_3_content_6"></string>

</resources>